When the lights go down, the inmates will rise.
Asylum Blackout is a horror, thriller film directed by Alexandre Courtes.
A group of cooks at an asylum for the criminally insane get locked
in with the inmates during a massive thunderstorm
George, played by Kenny Doughty.
Max, played by Rupert Evans.
J.B, played by Dave Legeno.
Harry, played by Richard Brake.
Pete, played by Darren Kent.
Lynn, played by Anna Skellern.
Asylum Blackout, also known as The Incident, is a 2011 English-language
horror film directed by Alexandre Courtès and written by S.
Craig Zahler.
The film explores themes of blackout, insane
asylum, flashlight, severed head, storm.
The tone is dark and intense.